They saw a chair, they saw a scream A white, white
boy silencing
They didn't see the brilliant light that burned
inside, so pure and bright.
They didn't hear your wicked wits or how the
puzzle pieces fit. They saw the shell, I saw the
pearl, the gun against a noisy world.
I don't see the boy they see I only see the best of
me Reflected in your knowing eyes Beneath the
clear and open skies I'll be your voice, I'll be
your shield A fortress that will never yield
They'll never know, they'll never find The
brilliant, beautiful boy inside
And when I'm with you in the night Beneath the
soft and fading light They see a line they think
we've crossed
A treasure gained, a virtue lost But they don't
know this sacred space This perfect time, this
perfect place
Reflected
The brilliant, beautiful boy inside.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Oh